Prince,
weren't you meeting His Majesty?
How did you get hurt?
I misspoke,
upsetting His Majesty,
so I was punished.
You're always
so careful with His Majesty.
Why this time...
Just leave.
I can do it myself.
Your injuries are all on your back.
Let me do it.
We've only been back to the capital for a few days.
The number of times you've been injured
is more than when you were leading troops in battle before.
Why don't we just go back to the border?
If you really can't bear to part with Miss Shen,
just take her with you.
If you keep talking,
go out and take your punishment.
Hold on.
I'll be more gentle.
I can do it myself.
You can go.
Don't move.
Be careful not to reopen the wound.
Your Highness
Are you in there?
Can I come in?
Clothes, clothes.
You can go.
Come in.
I'll leave him to you.
Your Highness,
are you hurt?
Just a scratch.
It's not a big deal.
What are you here for?
I heard that
Western Shu's peace terms this time
are to let you
marry the princess of the Western Shu
to marry the princess.
My brother summoned me to the palace today
to discuss this matter.
You don't want me to marry her?
Who you marry
has nothing to do with me.
If you really like the princess,
you'd better agree to this marriage.
Then the two countries can make peace,
and the people on the border
can live in peace.
You...
If you don't care about the marriage,
why do you visit me at night?
I want to ask you for permission
to visit Consort Dowager Li in Lingguo Temple.
You want to see my mother?
Why?
I still have doubts in my heart,
and I want to ask Consort Dowager Li in person.
Don't worry.
I'll just ask a few questions.
I won't disturb her peace.
But tomorrow is the first day of the month.
The Empress will take the concubines
and the female dependents of the court
to Lingguo Temple to pray for blessings.
Uninvited people
are not allowed to enter.
And now you
have lost your status as a legitimate daughter.
You absolutely cannot enter.
If you trust me,
I can
ask my mother for you.
Consort Dowager Li's accident
and my mother's death
both happened on the Day of Prayer.
There must be a secret in Lingguo Temple.
I trust you.
But I have an unjust case to solve.
In the past,
I just wanted my family to live
and the bad guys to be punished.
Now,
I also want to seek the truth for myself.
So I must meet Consort Dowager Li in person.
You must have a way to get me into the temple, right?
Besides,
you are not young anymore.
It's time to consider marriage.
I have been stationed at the border for many years
and have grown accustomed to military camp life.
Getting married and having children
is not what I want.
Prince Yu,
are you used to the life in the military camp,
or you just can't give up
the dignity of commanding the three armies?
Your Majesty, please understand.
I
didn't mean to refuse.
But
I already have someone in my heart.
I dare not let the Princess of the Western Regions down.
It's such a happy event.
why didn't you tell me earlier?
You almost made me pair the wrong couple.
You have a busy schedule.
I don't want to
bother you with this.
You
are my brother.
After father's death,
I
should take care of you more.
Unfortunately,
you were far away at the border.
As your elder brother,
I neglected to take care of you.
Now that you're back,
I'll make this marriage
for you.
I'll arrange this marriage for you
before the Western Shu Mission arrives.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I do have a way
to get you into Lingguo Temple legally.
It's up to you if you want to cooperate with me.
How?
Be my princess consort.
As long as you have this identity,
you can go in and out of Lingguo Temple
to visit your mother.
I'll be your princess consort,
what about the princess of Western Shu?
Many noble bachelors are at court.
There are many people more suitable than me
to be the emperor's son-in-law.
My brother
is eager to marry me to the princess of Western Shu.
It's just
to take back
my military power.
If you agree to be my princess,
you can help me keep my military power.
Then I can let you
enter Lingguo Temple
to visit my mother.
Our marriage
is just a temporary measure.
Once you achieve your goal,
you can leave as you please.
Only by finding the mastermind
can we save the Imperial Consort Dowager.
Fine,
I agree.
Lingguo Temple.
Miss, come and eat.
You're here.
Sit down and eat.
Okay.
Thank you, Your Highness.
After taking the medicinal diet,
do you feel better?
I've been feeling
much better.
You are
much more considerate than Zheng.
The decoction he sent
is bitter and hard to swallow.
Your idea is much better.
Medicine in food,
my tongue doesn't suffer anymore.
If Your Highness is in good health,
I'll be relieved.
You're not just
here to see me, are you?
To be honest,
I do have something to ask.
Do you remember
the last time
accompanying Her Majesty
who accompanied the Empress
to pray at Lingguo Temple?
On the first day of the lunar month,
the Empress, the Imperial Concubines,
the Imperial Princes and Princesses would come.
On the fifteenth day of the lunar month,
the Empress would bring some Imperial Concubines,
but the Imperial Princes and Princesses wouldn't come.
Other Imperial Relatives would avoid the first and the fifteenth.
The day when the Imperial Consort Dowager was attacked
was the fifteenth.
Your Highness.
We've just received a message from the temple.
Princess Consort didn't return last night.
This morning,
after the Imperial Consort Dowager informed us,
the temple has mobilized everyone to search.
But she's still missing.
Sui'er.
Let go, Sui'er.
It's me.
Sui'er.
You're awake.
You must have
had a hallucination just now.
Hallucination.
It's all an illusion.
It's taro powder.
Taro powder.
I finally saw clearly.
The person who killed me
was actually him.
Don't you want to explain
why you were there just now?
Your Highness.
Did you get anything out of it?
The nun insisted that
she mistook the intruder for a bad guy.
She insisted that
the hallucinogenic drug had nothing to do with her.
When I asked her a few more questions,
she bit her tongue and killed herself.
Since there is such a loyal dog,
it seems that the Lingguo Temple
has been infiltrated by a powerful master.
I'm pretty sure
the poison I was just hit with
is taro powder.
But the Second Prince is already dead.
His alchemy workshop has been closed.
The medicine of Ling Chuchu
was also found in the Prince Rui's Mansion.
Now the mansion has been closed,
and no one is allowed to get close.
Who else has this medicine?
Investigate it.
Yes.
Although I promised you
to not ask about your secret,
but since you are my princess consort,
you should cherish your life.
At least,
don't lose your life for nothing
before the Western Shu Mission leaves.
It was my carelessness this time.
But don't worry,
before we separate,
I will never cause you any trouble.
Don't be too arrogant.
I'm not afraid of any trouble.